Guide to the Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives 1950s-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives
1950s-2015
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG027-06-09
Central Washington University Relations
6.75 cubic feet 12 letter sized document boxes; 2 letter half sized document box; 2 audio cassette boxes; 21 legal sized document boxes, 11 Banker boxes,and 3 flat boxes Photographs, slides, negatives, audio cassettes, CD roms, and Zip drives in good condition
This collection consists of 8x10 and 4x6 inch photographic prints, slides, negatives, and digitial images produced and retained by the University Relations Office of Central Washington University from the 1950s to 2015.
Historical Note
Central Washington University's Advancement Office began as the Office of Public Service in 1938. In 1946 the office was renamed the Publications Office, a name which it retained until 1962 when it became part of the Office of Auxiliary Services. After 1966 it became the College Relations and Financial Aid Office and later, in 1969, the College Information Office. When Central Washington State College became a university in 1977, the office was renamed the University Information Office. In 1979 it was called the University Relations Office, and in 1993 it became the University Advancement Office.
The images represented in this collection depict Central's campus grounds and buildings, events on campus and the surrounding communities, faculty and staff, departmental and classroom activities and miscellaneous related photographs, slides and negatives. Included in the collection are promotional audio cassettes tapes developed during the 1970s and 1980s to promote academic programs at the university.
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
Organized alphabetically by subject
Open to the public for educational research
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University Relations
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Central Washington University--History; Universities and colleges--Washington (State)
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
Photographic prints; Slides; Negatives; Audiocassettes
- Academic Skills Center (Box-folder 1-1)
- Accounting (Box-folder 1-2)
- Aerial Photographs (Box-folder 1-3)
- Alumni (Box-folder 1-4)
- Alumni Scholarship (Box-folder 1-5)
- Anhui University – China (Box-folder 1-6)
- Anthropology (Box-folder 1-7)
- Archeology (Box-folder 1-8)
- Awards, honors and grants (Box-folder 1-9)
- Art (Box-folder 1-10)
- Barge Hall Ceremony (Box-folder 1-11)
- Baseball (Box-folder 1-12)
- Basketball (Box-folder 1-13)
- Biological Sciences (Box-folder 1-14)
- Biology (Box-folder 1-15)
- Boy State (Box-folder 1-16)
- Brooks, James (Box-folder 1-17)
- Business and Economics (Box-folder 1-18)
- Business Education (Box-folder 1-19)
- Business Week, 1985 (Box-folder 2-1)
- Business Week, 1985 (Box-folder 2-2)
- Business Week (Box-folder 2-3)
- Campus buildings (Box-folder 2-4)
- Campus buildings (Box-folder 2-5)
- Campus buildings – Barge Hall (Box-folder 2-6)
- Campus buildings – Courson Convention Center and Muzzall Hall (Box-folder 2-7)
- Campus buildings – Lind Hall (Box-folder 2-8)
- Campus buildings – McConnell Hall (Box-folder 2-9)
- Campus buildings – Residence Halls (Box-folder 2-10)
- Campus buildings – Shaw-Smyser Hall (Box-folder 2-11)
- Campus - Construction (Box-folder 3-1)
- Campus Crier (Box-folder 3-2)
- Campus, Miscellaneous – Negatives (Box-folder 3-3)
- Campus Scenes - Students (Box-folder 3-4)
- Campus Scenes - Students (Box-folder 3-5)
- Campus Scenes – Students (Box-folder 3-6)
- Campus - Winter Scenes (Box-folder 3-7)
- Central Investment Fund (Box-folder 3-8)
- CHCI (Box-folder 3-9)
- CHCI (Box-folder 3-10)
- Cheerleaders (Box-folder 3-11)
- Chemistry (Box-folder 3-12)
- Class trees (Box-folder 3-13)
- Classroom, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 3-14)
- Classroom – Negatives, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 4-1)
- Classroom – Negatives, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 4-2)
- Commencement, 1980s (Box-folder 4-3)
- Commencement, 1994 (Box-folder 4-4)
- Commencement, 1995 (Box-folder 4-5)
- Commencement, 1990s (Box-folder 4-6)
- Commencement (Box-folder 4-7)
- Communication (Box-folder 4-8)
- Communications Department, 1970s (Box-folder 4-9)
- Community events (Box-folder 4-10)
- Computer Science (Box-folder 4-11)
- Continuing Education (Box-folder 4-12)
- Convocation (Box-folder 4-13)
- Douglas Honors College (Box-folder 4-14)
- Drama (Box-folder 4-15)
- Drama (Box-folder 4-16)
- Drama – Negatives (Box-folder 5-1)
- Early Childhood Education (Box-folder 5-2)
- Education (Box-folder 5-3)
- Education Week (Box-folder 5-4)
- English (Box-folder 5-5)
- Environmental Studies (Box-folder 5-6)
- Ethnic Studies (Box-folder 5-7)
- Events – Negatives, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 5-8)
- Events, 1980 (Box-folder 5-9)
- Events, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 5-10)
- Events – Negatives, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 5-11)
- Events, 1981 (Box-folder 5-12)
- Events, 1982 (Box-folder 5-13)
- Events, 1983 (Box-folder 5-14)
- Events – Faculty and Staff, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 6-1)
- Events – News – Negatives, 1996 (Box-folder 6-2)
- Events – News – Negatives, 1997 (Box-folder 6-3)
- Events – News – Negatives, 1997 (Box-folder 6-4)
- Events – News – Negatives, 1998 (Box-folder 6-5)
- Events – News – Negatives, 1998 (Box-folder 6-6)
- Events – News – Negatives, 1999 (Box-folder 6-7)
- Events – News – Negatives, 1999 (Box-folder 6-8)
- Events – News – Negatives, 2000 (Box-folder 6-9)
- Events – News – Negatives, 2000 (Box-folder 7-1)
- Events – News – Negatives, 2000 (Box-folder 7-2)
- Events – News – Negatives, 2000 (Box-folder 7-3)
- Events (Box-folder 7-4)
- Events (Box-folder 7-5)
- Faculty (Box-folder 7-6)
- Faculty and Staff, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 7-7)
- Faculty and Staff – Unidentified (Box-folder 7-8)
- Faculty and Staff – Unidentified (Box-folder 7-9)
- Field Hockey (Box-folder 8-1)
- Financial Aid (Box-folder 8-2)
- Fires (Box-folder 8-3)
- Flight Technology (Box-folder 8-4)
- Football (Box-folder 8-5)
- Football – Negatives (Box-folder 8-6)
- Foundation – Gifts (Box-folder 8-7)
- Food Services (Box-folder 8-8)
- Foreign Language (Box-folder 8-9)
- Garrity, Donald (Box-folder 8-10)
- Garrity’s Scholarship Finalists (Box-folder 8-11)
- Geography (Box-folder 8-12)
- Geology (Box-folder 8-13)
- Girl’s State (Box-folder 8-14)
- Hall, Wendell (Box-folder 8-15)
- Health Center (Box-folder 8-16)
- Health Education (Box-folder 8-17)
- Hebeler Elementary School (Box-folder 8-18)
- Historical photographs (Box-folder 8-19)
- Homecoming, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 8-20)
- Homecoming – Negatives, 1980s (Box-folder 8-21)
- Home Economics (Box-folder 8-22)
- Indian Enrichment Conference (Box-folder 9-1)
- Individual Performers (Box-folder 9-2)
- Industrial and Engineering Technology (Box-folder 9-3)
- International Programs (Box-folder 9-4)
- Intramural Sports (Box-folder 9-5)
- International Programs (Box-folder 9-6)
- International Students (Box-folder 9-7)
- Japanese Garden (Box-folder 9-8)
- Library (Box-folder 9-9)
- Leisure Services (Box-folder 9-10)
- Mace (Box-folder 9-11)
- Mariners game (Box-folder 9-12)
- Mathematics (Box-folder 9-13)
- Minority Counseling (Box-folder 9-14)
- Music / Theater (Box-folder 9-15)
- Music / Theater (Box-folder 9-16)
- Music / Theater (Box-folder 9-17)
- Music / Theater (Box-folder 9-18)
- Nelson, Ivory (Box-folder 10-1)
- Occupational Education (Box-folder 10-2)
- Old photographs (Box-folder 10-3)
- Orchesis (Box-folder 10-4)
- Organization Development (Box-folder 10-5)
- Parents Association (Box-folder 10-6)
- Philosophy (Box-folder 10-7)
- Physical Education (Box-folder 10-8)
- Physics (Box-folder 10-9)
- Political Science (Box-folder 10-10)
- Psychology (Box-folder 10-11)
- Regional Archives (Box-folder 10-12)
- Registration – Preview Week (Box-folder 10-13)
- Religious Studies (Box-folder 10-14)
- Retirement Association (Box-folder 10-15)
- R.O.T.C. (Box-folder 10-16)
- Scholarships (Box-folder 10-17)
- School of Professional Studies (Box-folder 10-18)
- Science Education (Box-folder 10-19)
- Shaw-Smyser Opening (Box-folder 10-20)
- Shimane University – Japan (Box-folder 10-21)
- Soccer (Box-folder 10-22)
- Social Studies (Box-folder 10-23)
- Speakers (Box-folder 10-24)
- Special Education (Box-folder 10-25)
- Special Education (Box-folder 10-26)
- Student Activities (Box-folder 11-1)
- Student Activities (Box-folder 11-2)
- Student Recreation (Box-folder 11-3)
- Students – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 11-4)
- Summer theater (Box-folder 11-5)
- Suzuki Music School (Box-folder 11-6)
- Swimming (Box-folder 11-7)
- Swimming safety (Box-folder 11-8)
- Technology and Industrial Engineering (Box-folder 11-9)
- Technology and Industrial Engineering (Box-folder 11-10)
- Tennis (Box-folder 11-11)
- Track (Box-folder 11-12)
- Traffic and Security Office (Box-folder 11-13)
- Volleyball (Box-folder 11-14)
- Visitors Speakers and Entertainers (Box-folder 11-15)
- West Side Centers (Box-folder 11-16)
- Wieking, Robert (Box-folder 11-17)
- Women’s Basketball (Box-folder 11-18)
- Women’s Sports (Box-folder 11-19)
- Women’s Track and Field (Box-folder 11-20)
- Wrestling (Box-folder 11-21)
- Athletics – Slides, 1980s (Box-folder 12-1)
- Band and Theater - Slides (Box-folder 12-2)
- Basketball – Slides (Box-folder 12-3)
- Building and Grounds – Slides, 1960s-1980s (Box-folder 12-4)
- Building and Grounds – Slides, 1960s-1980s (Box-folder 12-5)
- CHCI (Box-folder 12-6)
- Classroom – Slides, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 12-7)
- Classroom and Library - Slides (Box-folder 12-8)
- Commencement - Slides, 1990s (Box-folder 12-9)
- Computer / Kaypro Van - Slides, 1980s (Box-folder 12-10)
- Events – Slides, 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 12-11)
- Events – Slides, 1980s (Box-folder 12-12)
- Events – Slides, 1984 (Box-folder 13-1)
- Events – Slides, 1986 (Box-folder 13-2)
- Events – Slides, 1993 (Box-folder 13-3)
- Faculty and Staff - Slides, 1960s-1980s (Box-folder 13-4)
- Flight Technology – Slides (Box-folder 13-5)
- Nelson, Ivory – Slides (Box-folder 13-6)
- Rodeo – Slides, 1950s (Box-folder 13-7)
- Winter Scenes – Slides (Box-folder 13-8)
- Miscellaneous – Slides (Box-folder 13-9)
- Central Investment Fund, 1983 (Box-folder 14-1)
- Teacher Education Program (Box-folder 14-2)
- Art Program (Box-folder 14-3)
- Foreign Languages Program (Box-folder 14-4)
- Anthropology Program (Box-folder 14-5)
- Audio Visual Division Program (Box-folder 14-6)
- Biological Science Program (Box-folder 14-7)
- Music Program (Box-folder 14-8)
- Central Investment Fund, 1984 (Box-folder 14-9)
- Central Investment Fund – James Brook Interview (Box-folder 14-10)
- CWSC Advertising Cuts, 1970s (Box-folder 14-11)
- CWSC Advertising Cuts, 1970s (Box-folder 14-12)
- BOD, Basketball, Blood drive, ROTC, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 15-1)
- Swimming, Wrestling, Basketball, Basketball, Cheer, Football, Parade, Volleyball, 1989- (Box-folder 15-2)
- Cheer, Chi-Rho, Track, Band, BOD, Theater, Performers, Fire Damage, 1986- (Box-folder 15-3)
- Seniors off of Campus, Theater, M.E.C.H.A., Hawaiian Daze, Campus Community, X-Mas Warefair, Swimming, Baseball, 1986- (Box-folder 15-4)
- Dining, Residence Halls, Swimming, Group Photos, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 15-5)
- Performers, Instructors, Campus, Alumni, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 15-6)
- Instructors, Continuing Education, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 15-7)
- Graduation, 1998- (Box-folder 15-8)
- Emerging Leaders, Residence Life, Dining Staff, Classroom Shots, Students, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 15-9)
- Student Union Building, BBQ, open House, Commencement, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 16-1)
- CHCI, Class Instruction, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 16-2)
- Students learning, Theater production, Preview Week, Campus Shots, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 16-3)
- Senior Ventures, Brochure Photos, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 16-4)
- Mcnair Scholarship winners, Theater Productions, Orchesis, Culture Fashion, Parent's Weekend, Preview Week, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 16-5)
- Residence Halls, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 16-6)
- Campus Maps, Campus Shots, 1996- (Box-folder 17-1)
- Basketball, Campus, Medical Center, Homecoming, Barbeque, Early Childhood Education, 1984- (Box-folder 17-2)
- Graduation, 1984- (Box-folder 17-3)
- Music Department, Moving in, Library Construction, Shaw Smyser, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 17-4)
- Music Class, 1999- (Box-folder 17-5)
- Drama, Snow, Campus, Barge Hall, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 17-6)
- Campus, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 17-7)
- Campus, Faculty Photos, Bookstore, 1996- (Box-folder 18-1)
- Faculty Photos, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 18-2)
- Faculty Photos, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 18-3)
- Faculty Photos, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 18-4)
- Faculty Photos, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 18-5)
- Faculty Photos, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 18-6)
- Faculty Photos, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 19-1)
- Faculty Photos, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 19-2)
- Faculty Photos, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 19-3)
- Faculty Photos, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 19-4)
- Faculty Photos, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 19-5)
- Campus, Students, Cover Photo, 1990- (Box-folder 20-1)
- Volleyball, Profiles, Action Shots, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 20-2)
- Black Hall, Physical Education Health Sciences, Senior Ventures, 1994- (Box-folder 20-3)
- CWU Graphics Production, Library, 1994- (Box-folder 20-4)
- Normal School, Music, Campus, WSNS Faculty, Library, 1891-1946 (Box-folder 20-5)
- Campus, Faculty, X-mas Ellensburg, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 20-6)
- Dean Nicholson, Boat Race, Band, Reslife, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 20-7)
- CHCI, Classroom, Early, Childhood Center, Geology Field Trip (Box-folder 20-8)
- Campus, Whitney Hall, Homecoming, Ellensburg, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 20-9)
- Senator Cantwell Visit, Sam Smith, Commencement, Students, Senior Ventures, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 20-10)
- Contact Sheets, 1993- (Box-folder 20-11)
- Contact Sheets, 1993- (Box-folder 20-12)
- contact Sheets, 1993- (Box-folder 20-13)
- CHCI, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 20-14)
- CHCI, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 20-15)
- CHCI, 1993- (Box-folder 21-1)
- contact Sheets, 1993- (Box-folder 21-2)
- Contact Sheets, 1993- (Box-folder 21-3)
- contact Sheets, 1993- (Box-folder 21-4)
- Sports Medicine, Physical Education, 1993- (Box-folder 21-5)
- Business Week, 1978- (Box-folder 21-6)
- IMC, Class Outside, Preview Week, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 22-1)
- Business Week, 1984- (Box-folder 22-2)
- Jim Hawkin's Laughing Horse, Archaeology, Field Trip, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 22-3)
- Senior Ventures, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 22-4)
- Business, Senior Ventures, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 22-5)
- Business Week, Fall Conference, Faculty, Library, 1964-1984 (Box-folder 22-6)
- Archaeology Trip, Campus Photos, Commencement, Hebeler Class, 1956-1997 (Box-folder 23-1)
- Media Center, Classes, Media Instruction, Business Week, 1973-1997 (Box-folder 23-2)
- Campus, President Activities, Theater, 1959-1987 (Box-folder 23-3)
- Campus, Library, Departments, Activities, 1956-2002 (Box-folder 23-4)
- Campus, Tennis Court, 1950- (Box-folder 23-5)
- Campus, Pres. Brooks, Student Life, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 24-1)
- Campus Art, Student Life, Building, 1970- (Box-folder 24-2)
- Faculty and Staff, Campus, Japanese Garden, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 24-3)
- CHCI, Campus, 1992- (Box-folder 24-4)
- Business Week, 1984- (Box-folder 24-5)
- Campus Building, Business Week, Media Center, 1961-1991 (Box-folder 24-6)
- Library Art, Rodeo, Orchestra, 1959-1987 (Box-folder 24-7)
- Business Week, Fall Conference, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 24-8)
- Basketball, Hall of Fame, Wrestling, East Asia Tour, Campus Carnival, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 25-1)
- Campus Shots, Athletics, Campus Art, Building, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 25-2)
- Conference Center, Western Days Fairgrounds, Homecoming, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 25-3)
- Conferences, Preview Week, Campus, 1993- (Box-folder 25-4)
- Conference Center, CHCI, Graduations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 25-5)
- Deep Sea Daze dining services, Residence Halls, Valley Shots, Conference, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 25-6)
- University Personnel, 1960- (Box-folder 26-1)
- University Faculty, 1950-1980 (Box-folder 26-2)
- University Personnel, CHCI, Senior Ventures, 1980- (Box-folder 26-3)
- University Faculty, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 26-4)
- University Faculty, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 26-5)
- Campus Shots, Graduation, Band, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 26-6)
- Preview Week, Wrestling, Basketball, 1990- (Box-folder 26-7)
- Campus Shots, 1990- (Box-folder 26-8)
- Reslife, 1990- (Box-folder 26-9)
- Reslife, Barge Hall, 1990- (Box-folder 26-10)
- Aerial Views of Campus, 1994- (Box-folder 26-11)
- Barge Hall, Lind Hall, 1995- (Box-folder 26-12)
- University Faculty, Personnel, 1990- (Box-folder 26-13)
- Barge Hall, Science Hall, Courson Hall, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 26-14)
- Faculty, Campus Shots, Centennial, Flood, 1990- (Box-folder 26-15)
- Dining Services, 1995- (Box-folder 26-16)
- Faculty, Senior Ventures, 1995- (Box-folder 26-17)
- Reslife, Faculty, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 26-18)
- President McIntyre, Wellington, international Students, 2000- (Box-folder 27-1)
- Rodeo Grounds, 2000- (Box-folder 27-2)
- Reslife Students, 2000- (Box-folder 27-3)
- Fire Damage, Campus Dorms, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 27-4)
- Snowy Campus, Construction, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 27-5)
- Science Hall, Halloween Events, Faculty, Satellite Campus, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 27-6)
- Faculty Photos, 1998- (Box-folder 27-7)
- Senior Ventures, 2000- (Box-folder 27-8)
- Reslife with President Nelson, 2001- (Box-folder 27-9)
- Music Faculty, Class Photos, Alumnis Spring Reunion, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 27-10)
- Wellington, Campus, Faculty, Orchestra, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 28-1)
- CHCI, 1995- (Box-folder 28-2)
- CHCI, Friends of Washoe, Goodall visit, 1995- (Box-folder 28-3)
- CHCI, Goodall Visit, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 28-4)
- CHCI, Reslife, President Garrity, President Nelson, Volleyball, Football, Aviation, Baseball, Swimming, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 28-5)
- Campus, Classroom Scenes, Commencement, Volleyball, Move in, Football, Library, Campus Art, Basketball, President Nelson, Track, Wrestling, CHCI, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 28-6)
- CHCI, Orchestra, Faculty, Student Life, Reslife, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 28-7)
- CHCI Enrichment Activities, 1995- (Box-folder 28-8)
- Imagine Production Photos, Dean Nicholson, Barge Hall, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 28-9)
- Women's Soccer, Commencement, Snowy Campus, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 28-10)
- Campus, Football Crowd, Sampler Event, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 29-1)
- Swimming, Faculty, Personnel Recognition, 1996- (Box-folder 29-2)
- Commencements, 1998- (Box-folder 29-3)
- Wildcat Welcome, 1996- (Box-folder 29-4)
- Staff Recognition, 2003- (Box-folder 29-5)
- Gov. Gary Locke Visit, Commencement, Snoqualmie Hall Construction, 1999- (Box-folder 29-6)
- Hunting Photo, Horse rider, Amputee Photo, 1902-1970 (Box-folder 29-7)
- Registration, 1990- (Box-folder 29-8)
- WSNS Photos, Football, Faculty, Campus, Picnic, 1894-1946 (Box-folder 29-9)
- Wikiup Campus Art, Golf, Classroom, 1940-1993 (Box-folder 29-10)
- Student Demonstration, Indigo Girls, Campus Art, Campus Tour, Student Life, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 29-11)
- Basketball, Volleyball, 2000- (Box-folder 29-12)
- Language and Literature Building Remodel, Source, 1998- (Box-folder 29-13)
- Campus Police Training, 2002- (Box-folder 29-14)
- Friends of the Library Book Sale, Campus, 2002- (Box-folder 29-15)
- Physical Education and Health Studies, 1999- (Box-folder 29-16)
- Faculty, Swimming, Basketball, Band, Dick and Janes, MECHA, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 29-17)
- Football, Lind Hall, Coursen and Muzzall Hall, Wildcat Welcome, Basketball, Commencement, Staff Recognition, Student Life, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 30-1)
- Movers and Shakers, Spurgeon Gallery, Conference Program, Aviation, Commencement, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 30-2)
- Downtown BBQ, Faculty Photos, Alumni, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 30-3)
- Faculty Photos, university Personnel, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 30-4)
- Movers and Shakers, Commencement, Freshman Orientation, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 30-5)
- Chief Tsugani, native Art, Ceremony for Totem Pole Installation, 1999- (Box-folder 30-6)
- Faculty Photos, 1940-1990 (Box-folder 30-7)
- Campus, Movers and Shakers, Freshman Welcome, Downtown BBQ, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 31-1)
- Xmas in Barge, Lifelong Learning, Commencement, 1998- (Box-folder 31-2)
- Science Faculty, Downtown BBQ, Commencement Ceremony, Source, 1999- (Box-folder 31-3)
- Campus, Dining Services, Football, Science Faculty, 1999- (Box-folder 31-4)
- Maria Cantwell Visit, Vietnam War Memorial, Football, Open House, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 31-5)
- Band, Campus, Faculty, Football, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 31-6)
- Baseball, Commencement, Campus Art, Volleyball, Wildcat Welcome, Football, 1999- (Box-folder 31-7)
- CWU Campus Negatives and Photos, 1994- (Box-folder 31-8)
- Campus, Student Life, Downtown BBQ, Wikiup, 1993- (Box-folder 31-9)
- Scholars Recognition Ceremony, 2000- (Box-folder 31-10)
- Faculty visit Grade School, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 31-11)
- Volleyball, preview Week, Snowy Campus, Wrestling, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 31-12)
- Basketball, Campus, Crowds, Employee Recognition, Commencement, Cheerleaders, Faculty, War Memorial, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 32-1)
- Orchestra Faculty, Barge hall, McConnell hall, 1990-2005 (Box-folder 32-2)
- Paul Baker, memorial Service, 2003- (Box-folder 32-3)
- Aviation, Midstate Aviation, 2001- (Box-folder 32-4)
- Faculty, Alumni Staff, Art, 2001- (Box-folder 32-5)
- Hall of Fame, Commencement, Basketball, Band, 2002- (Box-folder 32-6)
- Science Hall, Barge Hall, Nicholson Pavilion, 2000- (Box-folder 32-7)
- Realife, Petroglyph, 1990- (Box-folder 32-8)
- WSNS, Faculty Photos, 1892-1980 (Box-folder 32-9)
- Alumni, Student Life, Campus, Mammoth Art, Classroom, Reslife, 1992- (Box-folder 32-10)
- Alumni and Faculty, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 32-11)
- Student Life, CIF Scholarship Winners, 1996- (Box-folder 32-12)
- Basketball, Football, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 32-13)
- Flood Photos, 1990- (Box-folder 33-1)
- Tibetan Monks, Aviation, Visiting Authors, 1990- (Box-folder 33-2)
- Reslife, Orchestra, Theater, 1990- (Box-folder 33-3)
- Barge Hall, Reslife, Theater, Physical Therapy, 1990- (Box-folder 33-4)
- Manastash Art, 1996- (Box-folder 33-5)
- Student Life, Commencement, Classrooms, Health Center, 1996- (Box-folder 33-6)
- Brooks Library, Lynnwood Center, 1990- (Box-folder 33-7)
- Faculty, Reslife, 1990- (Box-folder 33-8)
- Commencement, Student Life, Reslife, 1995- (Box-folder 33-9)
- Music Faculty, 1999- (Box-folder 33-10)
- Campus Grilling, Student Life, Faculty and Personnel, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 33-11)
- Faculty, Reslife, 1990- (Box-folder 33-12)
- Student Life, Reslife, 1990- (Box-folder 33-13)
- Radio, Student Activities, Reslife, 1990- (Box-folder 33-14)
- Reslife, Downtown, BBQ, 1994- (Box-folder 33-15)
- Campus, Faculty, Reslife, 1993- (Box-folder 34-1)
- Campus Underground, 1990- (Box-folder 34-2)
- Campus, Student Life, 1990- (Box-folder 34-3)
- Basketball, football, Track and Field, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 34-4)
- Commencement, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 34-5)
- Faculty, Student Life, 1970-2000 (Box-folder 34-6)
- Reslife, Student Activities, 1970- (Box-folder 34-7)
- Lind Hall, Science Hall, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 34-8)
- Archives, Campus, Art, 1994- (Box-folder 34-9)
- Campus Police, Staff Recognition, 2001- (Box-folder 34-10)
- CHCI, Friends of Washoe, 1998- (Box-folder 34-11)
- ROTC, 1999- (Box-folder 34-12)